The Truth Hurts
Get Carter is a action, drama, thriller film directed by Stephen Kay.
Jack Carter, a mob enforcer living in Las Vegas, travels back to
his hometown of Seattle for his brother's funeral.
During this visit, Carter realizes that the death of his
brother was not accidental, but a murder.
With this knowledge, Carter sets out to kill all those responsible.
Jack Carter, played by Sylvester Stallone.
Gloria Carter, played by Miranda Richardson.
Doreen Carter, played by Rachael Leigh Cook.
Jeremy Kinnear, played by Alan Cumming.
Cyrus Paice, played by Mickey Rourke.
Con McCarty, played by John C. McGinley.
Get Carter is a 2000 American neo-noir action thriller film directed by Stephen Kay, written by David
McKenna, and starring Sylvester Stallone, Rachael Leigh Cook, Alan Cumming, Mickey Rourke, John C.
McGinley, Rhona Mitra, and Michael Caine.
Based on the Ted Lewis' novel Jack's Return Home, the film is a remake of the
1971 film of the same name, in which Caine played the title role.
The film was released in the United States by Morgan Creek Productions, Inc.
(through Warner Bros.
Pictures) on October 6, 2000.
It was panned by critics and the film flopped at the box office, with worldwide earnings of
approximately $19.4 million against a production budget of $63.6 million.
The film explores themes of ritual, pornographic video, car crash, remake.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional and intense.